Workers Education Bureau of America Records 5277
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III. Publications and Research
  - Commission on Occupied Areas, American Council on Education 1 of 2, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Commission on Occupied Areas, American Council on Education 2 of 2, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Commission on Occupied Areas, American Council on Education, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Case Studies in Collective Bargaining, U.B. Stone, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 2)